Viewers all over the world,
wherever you are, I want to start from you.
Whatever situation, wherever you are right now, begin to come against every infirmity in your life.
Viewers all over the world,
begin to come against every infirmity,
every spirit that stands against you...
every spirit that hinders you way...
every spirit that hinders you...
every spirit that causes you limitation...
every spirit that causes you shortcomings.
Viewers all over the world, begin to stand against
every spirit in the name of Jesus.
Right now, order that spirit to go.
Begin to order that spirit to go right now.
That spirit of killing, stealing, destruction...
that spirit that causes you setback...
that spirit that causes you shortcomings.
Begin to order the spirit in the name of Jesus.
I order the spirit out of your life, career, business
and finances in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name.
Viewers all over the world, confess your freedom.
Confess your freedom right now.
Viewers all over the world,
where can you go from His presence?
Every hidden sickness in your body...
every hidden disease in your body...
every hidden affliction in your
system, I command them out!
I command them out!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name.
In your blood.
Out!
In your kidney.
In your liver.
Out!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name.
Rejoice!
Confess your healing.
Viewers all over the world, you have been
claiming your right;
there is nothing wrong with that.
You can claim your right
but don't hold unto an offence.
Whether you are right or wrong,
you have have no right to hold onto an offence.
You must be free from offence.
Offences imprison you-self imprisonment.
When you hold onto an offence,
you have imprisoned yourself.
Offence of this.
Offence of that.
You have imprisoned yourself.
The Bible says, our spirit must be free -
free to contact the Spirit of God.
Viewers, listen! Your spirit must be free.
I am not saying that you should not claim your right,
but don't hold onto an offence.
Offences imprison one.
Your spirit must be free from all offences.
Wrong accusation, whatever it is,
whether you are right or wrong,
your spirit must be free to contact the Spirit of God.
I release you in the name of Jesus!
I release your spirit from the pain of the past!
I release your spirit from past accusation!
I release your spirit from the pain of the past,
past persecution, past pain - be released
I say to your spirit, be released!
Be released!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name.
In the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name.
I know you are going through major trouble,
hatred, persecution.
Whatever you are going through - misjudged or whatever -
you have no right to hold an offence.
I release you from the pain of the past, in the name of Jesus.
I release you from hurt.
I mean deep hurt, in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name.
There is hurt, and then there is deep hurt.
Someone will say, I can never forgive them.
No, no, no, no no.
That is deep hurt.
I release you from hurt, deep hurt, in the name of Jesus!
Be released from hurt, deep hurt in Jesus name!
Rejoice.
Pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua,
Touch your screen by faith in Jesus' name.
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit,
and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God, as you send your testimony.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today;
and stay to up-to-date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances,
sermons, and testimonies from The SCOAN
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.